And last year was the
first year obviously that we
did this and it was
a very cool moment.
And Madden's been working hard
at new drawing, always individual
characters and buddies. I think
he's got logos of every
team in the NFL. He
drew the NFL logo for
every team as well. And
Madden's going to be drawing
for us throughout the shift.
Do you have to put
the doink right next to
your dad's head? Okay, well
I don't blame you. Manicue
words. Exactly. I mean, he
didn't, but there's also a
bake in there. So that
might- And
I want to tell this
to Hunter, Noah, Lenny, and
Mom if they're
watching this. Mom,
I love you.
Hunter,
you're my favorite twin.
Noah,
I do like you and
Lennon for
supporting me.